# Haritha Thankachan

**Software Engineer** 

Cochin7907086096→ harithak17@gmail.com

Successful Software Engineer offering 5years of experience in demanding environments. Skilled in directing development with creative and performance-oriented approach. Well-organized and customer-focused with proven skills in project development and team activities. Completed B-tech in Information Technology.

### **Skills**

- JAVA
- Hibernate
- MySql
- Primefaces
- Servlets
- Webservices
- Oracle
- CSS

- Spring Boot
- REST
- JSP
- Javascript

## Work experience

#### **BEO Software PVT LTD**

Jan 2019 - Sept 2021

#### **Software Engineer**

Atlas is a software for Customs operations exclusively for German clients. Customs clearance for Import and Export is being done through the application which interacts directly with the Zoll[German customs].

- Development and Support for the Live Enterprise Application ATLAS
- Design and development of new messages.
- Ensuring test coverage and code quality using SonarQube
- Database techonology: Mysql and IDE: Eclipse IDE.

#### **Dantek Technologies**

Jan 2016 - Oct 2018

#### Java Developer

It is a web based application. It is based on ERP business process. It includes product management, supply chain (purchasing, manufacturing, distribution) financials, warehouse management, sales order processing, and Quality and Testing.

- Development and Implementation of various modules.
- Generating graphical representation of data.
- Generating pdf, excel reports of data.
- Database techonology: MySql and IDE: Netbeans.

# G Tec Computer Educations

May 2014 - Dec 2015

#### **Software Programming Faculty**

IT education network providing training and meaningful certification in Software, Accounting, Hardware, Multimedia, CAD, Mobile Technology and Language skills.

- Guided academic projects for BCA students in VB6.
- Trained DCA,PGDCA students.
- Trained students in Computer basics, Programming basics and open office.

### Education

# Toc H Institute of Science & Technology

2009 - 2013

## B.Tech in Information Technology

Graduated from CUSAT university with 64% marks.

## BHSS Kalady

2006 - 2008

#### **Higher Secondary Education**

HSE from Board of Public Examinations, Kerala in 2008 with 72% marks.

#### **BHSS Kalady**

1997 - 2006

#### **SSLC**

S.S.L.C from Board of Public Examinations, Kerala in 2006 with 70% marks